[{"prompt": "the", "choices": ["la", "historia", "matem\u00e1ticas", "geograf\u00eda"], "correctIndex": 0, "type": "assist", "difficulty": 1.0, "categories": ["education"], "goals": ["school"]}, {"prompt": "of", "choices": ["de", "historia", "matem\u00e1ticas", "geograf\u00eda"], "correctIndex": 0, "type": "assist", "difficulty": 0.57, "categories": ["education"], "goals": ["school"]}, {"prompt": "and", "choices": ["y", "historia", "matem\u00e1ticas", "geograf\u00eda"], "correctIndex": 0, "type": "assist", "difficulty": 0.56, "categories": ["education"], "goals": ["school"]}, {"prompt": "to", "choices": ["a", "historia", "matem\u00e1ticas", "geograf\u00eda"], "correctIndex": 0, "type": "assist", "difficulty": 0.52, "categories": ["education"], "goals": ["school"]}, {"prompt": "in", "choices": ["en", "historia", "matem\u00e1ticas", "geograf\u00eda"], "correctIndex": 0, "type": "assist", "difficulty": 0.37, "categories": ["education"], "goals": ["school"]}, {"prompt": "for", "choices": ["en lugar de", "historia", "matem\u00e1ticas", "geograf\u00eda"], "correctIndex": 0, "type": "assist", "difficulty": 0.26, "categories": ["education"], "goals": ["school"]}, {"prompt": "is", "choices": ["es", "historia", "matem\u00e1ticas", "geograf\u00eda"], "correctIndex": 0, "type": "assist", "difficulty": 0.2, "categories": ["education"], "goals": ["school"]}, {"prompt": "on", "choices": ["el", "historia", "matem\u00e1ticas", "geograf\u00eda"], "correctIndex": 0, "type": "assist", "difficulty": 0.16, "categories": ["education"], "goals": ["school"]}, {"prompt": "that", "choices": ["que", "historia", "matem\u00e1ticas", "geograf\u00eda"], "correctIndex": 0, "type": "assist", "difficulty": 0.15, "categories": ["education"], "goals": ["school"]}, {"prompt": "by", "choices": ["por", "historia", "matem\u00e1ticas", "geograf\u00eda"], "correctIndex": 0, "type": "assist", "difficulty": 0.14, "categories": ["education"], "goals": ["school"]}, {"prompt": "this", "choices": ["esto", "historia", "matem\u00e1ticas", "geograf\u00eda"], "correctIndex": 0, "type": "assist", "difficulty": 0.14, "categories": ["education"], "goals": ["school"]}, {"prompt": "with", "choices": ["con", "historia", "matem\u00e1ticas", "geograf\u00eda"], "correctIndex": 0, "type": "assist", "difficulty": 0.14, "categories": ["education"], "goals": ["school"]}, {"prompt": "you", "choices": ["t\u00fa", "historia", "matem\u00e1ticas", "geograf\u00eda"], "correctIndex": 0, "type": "assist", "difficulty": 0.13, "categories": ["education"], "goals": ["school"]}, {"prompt": "not", "choices": ["no", "historia", "matem\u00e1ticas", "geograf\u00eda"], "correctIndex": 0, "type": "assist", "difficulty": 0.11, "categories": ["education"], "goals": ["school"]}, {"prompt": "or", "choices": ["o", "historia", "matem\u00e1ticas", "geograf\u00eda"], "correctIndex": 0, "type": "assist", "difficulty": 0.11, "categories": ["education"], "goals": ["school"]}, {"prompt": "be", "choices": ["# Ser # # Ser # # Ser # # Ser # # Ser # Ser #  # Ser # Ser # # Ser # Ser # Ser # Ser # Ser # Ser # Ser # Ser # Ser # Ser # Ser # Ser # Ser # Ser # Ser # Ser # Ser # Ser # Ser # Ser # Ser # Ser       # Ser # Ser  # Ser       # Ser  # Ser   # Ser   # Ser  # Ser   # Ser  # Ser   # Ser  # Ser    # Ser    # Ser    # Ser      # Ser     # Ser        # Ser        # Ser  # Ser          # Ser   # Ser", "historia", "matem\u00e1ticas", "geograf\u00eda"], "correctIndex": 0, "type": "assist", "difficulty": 0.1, "categories": ["education"], "goals": ["school"]}, {"prompt": "are", "choices": ["son", "historia", "matem\u00e1ticas", "geograf\u00eda"], "correctIndex": 0, "type": "assist", "difficulty": 0.1, "categories": ["education"], "goals": ["school"]}, {"prompt": "from", "choices": ["desde", "historia", "matem\u00e1ticas", "geograf\u00eda"], "correctIndex": 0, "type": "assist", "difficulty": 0.1, "categories": ["education"], "goals": ["school"]}, {"prompt": "at", "choices": ["en el", "historia", "matem\u00e1ticas", "geograf\u00eda"], "correctIndex": 0, "type": "assist", "difficulty": 0.1, "categories": ["education"], "goals": ["school"]}, {"prompt": "as", "choices": ["como", "historia", "matem\u00e1ticas", "geograf\u00eda"], "correctIndex": 0, "type": "assist", "difficulty": 0.1, "categories": ["education"], "goals": ["school"]}, {"prompt": "your", "choices": ["tu", "historia", "matem\u00e1ticas", "geograf\u00eda"], "correctIndex": 0, "type": "assist", "difficulty": 0.09, "categories": ["education"], "goals": ["school"]}, {"prompt": "all", "choices": ["todos", "historia", "matem\u00e1ticas", "geograf\u00eda"], "correctIndex": 0, "type": "assist", "difficulty": 0.09, "categories": ["education"], "goals": ["school"]}, {"prompt": "have", "choices": ["tener", "historia", "matem\u00e1ticas", "geograf\u00eda"], "correctIndex": 0, "type": "assist", "difficulty": 0.07, "categories": ["education"], "goals": ["school"]}, {"prompt": "new", "choices": ["nuevo", "historia", "matem\u00e1ticas", "geograf\u00eda"], "correctIndex": 0, "type": "assist", "difficulty": 0.07, "categories": ["education"], "goals": ["school"]}, {"prompt": "more", "choices": ["m\u00e1s", "historia", "matem\u00e1ticas", "geograf\u00eda"], "correctIndex": 0, "type": "assist", "difficulty": 0.07, "categories": ["education"], "goals": ["school"]}, {"prompt": "was", "choices": ["era", "historia", "matem\u00e1ticas", "geograf\u00eda"], "correctIndex": 0, "type": "assist", "difficulty": 0.06, "categories": ["education"], "goals": ["school"]}, {"prompt": "we", "choices": ["nosotros", "historia", "matem\u00e1ticas", "geograf\u00eda"], "correctIndex": 0, "type": "assist", "difficulty": 0.06, "categories": ["education"], "goals": ["school"]}, {"prompt": "home", "choices": ["Inicio", "historia", "matem\u00e1ticas", "geograf\u00eda"], "correctIndex": 0, "type": "assist", "difficulty": 0.06, "categories": ["education"], "goals": ["school"]}, {"prompt": "can", "choices": ["puede", "historia", "matem\u00e1ticas", "geograf\u00eda"], "correctIndex": 0, "type": "assist", "difficulty": 0.05, "categories": ["education"], "goals": ["school"]}, {"prompt": "us", "choices": ["nosotros", "historia", "matem\u00e1ticas", "geograf\u00eda"], "correctIndex": 0, "type": "assist", "difficulty": 0.05, "categories": ["education"], "goals": ["school"]}, {"prompt": "about", "choices": ["acerca de", "historia", "matem\u00e1ticas", "geograf\u00eda"], "correctIndex": 0, "type": "assist", "difficulty": 0.05, "categories": ["education"], "goals": ["school"]}, {"prompt": "if", "choices": ["si", "historia", "matem\u00e1ticas", "geograf\u00eda"], "correctIndex": 0, "type": "assist", "difficulty": 0.05, "categories": ["education"], "goals": ["school"]}, {"prompt": "page", "choices": ["p\u00e1gina", "historia", "matem\u00e1ticas", "geograf\u00eda"], "correctIndex": 0, "type": "assist", "difficulty": 0.05, "categories": ["education"], "goals": ["school"]}, {"prompt": "my", "choices": ["mi", "historia", "matem\u00e1ticas", "geograf\u00eda"], "correctIndex": 0, "type": "assist", "difficulty": 0.05, "categories": ["education"], "goals": ["school"]}, {"prompt": "has", "choices": ["tiene", "historia", "matem\u00e1ticas", "geograf\u00eda"], "correctIndex": 0, "type": "assist", "difficulty": 0.05, "categories": ["education"], "goals": ["school"]}, {"prompt": "search", "choices": ["buscar", "historia", "matem\u00e1ticas", "geograf\u00eda"], "correctIndex": 0, "type": "assist", "difficulty": 0.04, "categories": ["education"], "goals": ["school"]}, {"prompt": "free", "choices": ["libre", "historia", "matem\u00e1ticas", "geograf\u00eda"], "correctIndex": 0, "type": "assist", "difficulty": 0.04, "categories": ["education"], "goals": ["school"]}, {"prompt": "but", "choices": ["pero", "historia", "matem\u00e1ticas", "geograf\u00eda"], "correctIndex": 0, "type": "assist", "difficulty": 0.04, "categories": ["education"], "goals": ["school"]}, {"prompt": "our", "choices": ["nuestra", "historia", "matem\u00e1ticas", "geograf\u00eda"], "correctIndex": 0, "type": "assist", "difficulty": 0.04, "categories": ["education"], "goals": ["school"]}, {"prompt": "one", "choices": ["uno", "historia", "matem\u00e1ticas", "geograf\u00eda"], "correctIndex": 0, "type": "assist", "difficulty": 0.04, "categories": ["education"], "goals": ["school"]}, {"prompt": "other", "choices": ["otros", "historia", "matem\u00e1ticas", "geograf\u00eda"], "correctIndex": 0, "type": "assist", "difficulty": 0.04, "categories": ["education"], "goals": ["school"]}, {"prompt": "do", "choices": ["@info: tooltip", "historia", "matem\u00e1ticas", "geograf\u00eda"], "correctIndex": 0, "type": "assist", "difficulty": 0.04, "categories": ["education"], "goals": ["school"]}, {"prompt": "information", "choices": ["informaci\u00f3n", "historia", "matem\u00e1ticas", "geograf\u00eda"], "correctIndex": 0, "type": "assist", "difficulty": 0.04, "categories": ["education"], "goals": ["school"]}, {"prompt": "time", "choices": ["hora", "historia", "matem\u00e1ticas", "geograf\u00eda"], "correctIndex": 0, "type": "assist", "difficulty": 0.04, "categories": ["education"], "goals": ["school"]}, {"prompt": "they", "choices": ["ellos", "historia", "matem\u00e1ticas", "geograf\u00eda"], "correctIndex": 0, "type": "assist", "difficulty": 0.04, "categories": ["education"], "goals": ["school"]}]